不久前，你来到迈阿密国际，似乎发生了很多事情，但也没有发生那么多。
A while ago, it seems like a lot happened, it didn't happen that much, that you arrived at Inter Miami.
Hace un tiempo, ya parece que pasó mucho, no pasó tanto, que llegaste al Inter de Miami.
啊，足球。
Ah, football.
Ah, de fútbol.
好吧，我以为我是带着这些废话来的。
Ok, I thought I was coming with that nonsense.
Ok, pensé que venía con esa boludece.
来吧，走吧。
Come on, go.
Dale, vete.
没有废话。
There is no nonsense.
No hay boludece.
没有，有，有。
There is no, there is, there is.
No hay, hay, hay.
啊，两个都来了。
Ah, both are coming.
Ah, viene las dos.
你和 Leo 谈论世界杯。
You talk to Leo about the World Cup.
Vos hablas con Leo del Mundial.
很多。
a lot.
mucho.
我的生活离不开世界杯，我认为……
I didn't live without thinking about the World Cup and I think that...
No viví sin pensar en la Copa del Mundo y yo creo que...
国家队又将成为主角。
that the national team is going to be the protagonist again.
que la selección va a ser protagonista otra vez.
我过得很开心，有时我什至会告诉你
I'm having a great time, I would even tell you that sometimes
Llevo en un gran momento, hasta te diría que a veces
甚至比其他比赛还要好。
even better than in other competitions.
hasta mejor que en otras competiciones.
你是否考虑在某个时候重返赛车界？
Are you thinking about returning to Racing at some point?
¿Tenés pensado a la vuelta de Racing en algún momento?
我不是一个灰色或冷漠的人。
I'm not a gray or lukewarm guy.
No soy un tipo ni gris ni tibio.
日期或者是否会发生......
Date or if it will happen...
Fecha o si va a suceder...
我不知道，不。
I don't know, no.
No lo sé, no.
我不做未来的赞美。
I do not make future praise.
No hago futuro elogio.
谁赢了？
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
罗德里戈？
Rodrigo?
¿Rodrigo?
我可以走了吗？
-  -
为你。
Can I go?
¿Puedo ir?
不，现在就离开这里，认真的。
For you.
Para vos.
现在说实话，说实话。
No, get out of here, seriously now.
No, fuera de aquí, ahora en serio.
我杀了他，我杀了他！
Now seriously, for the truth.
Ahora en serio, para la verdad.
给鸡。
-  -
你在干什么？
I killed him, I killed him!
¡Lo maté, lo maté!
你知道吗，很多人因为你，不说好坏，就骂我鸡鸡？
To the chicken.
A la chicken.
而很多品牌也因为我而给你打电话。
What are you doing?
¿Qué haces?
我没有再告诉自己这个坏消息。
-  -
作为？
Do you know that many people because of you, I'm not saying whether it's good or bad, they call me chicken?
¿Sabes que mucha gente por tu culpa, no digo sea bueno o malo, me dice chicken?
不，但这是萨满，但停下来。
And many brands also call you because of me.
Y muchas marcas te llaman también por mi culpa.
进展顺利。
I didn't tell myself the bad news anymore.
No me conté las malas nada más.
我要训练你吗？
-  -
我不知道。
As?
¿Cómo?
我的意思是...
No, but it's Shaman, but stop.
No, pero es Shaman, pero para.
你说得有道理。
It went well.
Fue bien.
你说得有道理。
Shall I train you?
¿Te entreno?
正如罗德里一样，不久前似乎发生了很多事情，但又似乎没有发生太多事情。
I don't know.
Yo no sé.
你到达了迈阿密国际。
I mean...
O sea...
我想问你，这个城市怎么样？
I want to ask you how you are with the city.
Te quiero preguntar cómo estás con la ciudad.
啊，足球。
Ah, football.
Ah, de fútbol.
好吧，我以为我是带着这些废话来的。
Ok, I thought I was coming with that nonsense.
Ok, pensé que venía con esa boludece.
来吧，走吧。
Come on, go.
Dale, vete.
没有废话！
There is no nonsense!
¡No hay boludece!
是双的。
-  -
你好吗？
It's double.
Es la doble.
你在迈阿密还好吗？
How are you?
¿Cómo estás?
你在俱乐部怎么样？
How are you in Miami?
¿Cómo estás en Miami?
好，非常好。
How are you at the club?
¿Cómo estás en el club?
快乐，享受。
Good, very good.
Bien, muy bien.
目标，我到达了，很快我们就成为了冠军，所以也是如此。
Happy, enjoying.
Contento, disfrutando.
激励人心，世界杯即将来临。
objectives, I arrived and in a short time we became champions, so that too.
objetivos, llegué y al poquito tiempo salimos campeones, así que eso también.
很多超级可爱的东西。
motivates, the World Cup is coming.
motiva, viene la Copa del Mundo.
这确实必须是一个决定，因为人们想象......
Lots of super cute things.
Un montón de cosas superlindas.
你有各种各样的报价。
It really has to be a decision because one imagines that...
Realmente tiene que ser una decisión porque uno imagina que...
你说，我要去这里。
that you had offers of all kinds.
que tenías como ofertas de todo tipo.
是的，让我们看看，已经有很多俱乐部和地方了。
You said, I'm going here.
Dijiste, voy acá.
有一件事超越了这一切。
Yes, let's see, there have been a lot of clubs and places.
Sí, a ver, sí que ha habido un montón de clubes y de lugares.
它正在与最伟大的球员并肩作战。
There is one thing that surpasses all that.
Hay una cosa que sobrepasa todo eso.
那是一个...
And that's one...
Y esa es una...
我相信世界上任何球员、任何人都想要这样的机会。
An opportunity that I believe that any player in the world, any person, wants.
Una oportunidad que yo creo que cualquier jugador del mundo, cualquier persona, la quiere.
他想要活下去，我已经吸取了教训，我不会放过任何一个......
He wants to live and I had that lesson and I wasn't going to let one go...
Quiere vivir y yo tenía esa lección y no iba a dejar pasar una...
类似的情况加上我也是朋友所以
a situation like that plus being a friend to me too so
una situación así más siendo un amigo para mí también así que
对我来说，每天和他一起在球场上是一个梦想。
For me, every day sharing a court with him is a dream.
Para mí, todos los días compartir una cancha con él es un sueño.
他拥有足球运动员所寻找的最可爱的东西。
and he has the cutest thing a soccer player looks for.
y tiene lo más lindo que busca un jugador de fútbol que es.
生活在惊喜之中，接受你不知道将会发生什么的事实。
Live with the surprise, with the fact that you don't know what is going to be or happen.
Convivir con la sorpresa, con que no sabes lo que va a ser o va a pasar.
总是让你感到惊讶的是，它真的很好。
So surprising you all the time for the better is that it's really good.
Entonces sorprenderte todo el tiempo para bien es que está buenísimo.
谁推动了奥莱奥或贝克汉姆？
Who pushed Oleo or Beckham?
¿Quién metió el push de Oleo o Beckham?
谁推动了Che？
Who put Che's push?
¿Quién metió el push de Che?
来吧，罗德里戈，来吧，我已经为你准备好了一切。
Come on, Rodrigo, come, I've got everything for you.
Vamos, Rodrigo, venite, que te tengo todo.
不，那是……那是……
No, it was... It was...
No, fue... Fue...
这是一切的选择，我想显然是我先和 Leo 讨论过的。
It was a choice of everything, I guess obviously I talked about it with Leo first.
Fue una elección de todo, supongo obviamente que primero lo hablé con Leo.
好吧，正如梅西所理解的那样，他显然也在等着看，我想继续留在欧洲。
And well, he was obviously also waiting to see, as Messi understood, I wanted to continue in Europe.
Y bueno, él obviamente también esperando a ver, como entendiendo Messi, yo quería seguir en Europa.
当他从我这边看到有这种可能性时，我...
when he saw from my side that there was that possibility, that I was...
cuando vio de mi lado que existía esa posibilidad, que yo estaba...
我确信我想让这成为现实。
I was convinced that I wanted to make that a reality.
Estaba convencido de que quería hacer realidad eso.
老板和俱乐部的许多人都出现了。
The owners and many people from the club appear.
Aparecen los dueños y mucha gente del club.
来实现这个想法。
to carry out that idea.
a llevar a cabo esa idea.
我们今天来看这个记录笔记。
We come to today this recorded note.
Llegamos a hoy esta nota grabada.
距世界杯还有 42 天，这种情况随时可能发生。
42 days before the World Cup and this can always happen.
a 42 días del Mundial y siempre esto puede haber.
我在许多混合区看到你说他们像球员一样问你，你说，别再犯傻了，因为我也是粉丝。
I saw you in many of your mixed zones saying that they asked you like a player and you said, stop stupid, because I'm a fan too.
Te vi en muchas zonas mixtas tuyas diciendo que te preguntaban como un jugador y vos decías, pará boludo, porque yo soy un hincha también.
发生的事情是有一个手柄。
And what's happening is there's a handle.
Y lo que está pasando es que hay una manija.
好吧，有些人会拥有它，其他人不会，我也不想陷入争论，我说，但是......
Well, some will have it, others won't, I also don't want to get into a debate, I say, but...
Bueno, algunos la tendrán, otros no, también no quiero entrar en debate, digo, pero...
尤其是世界杯即将到来。
particularly the world cup is coming.
particularmente se viene el mundial.
阿根廷如何到达？
How does Argentina arrive?
¿Cómo llega Argentina?
你准备如何？
How do you prepare?
¿Cómo te preparas?
你已经说了？
You already say?
¿Ya decís?
嘿，就是这样。
Hey, that's it.
Che, ya es.
你说的事情发生在你身上，就是这样。
It happens to you that you say, that's it.
Te pasa eso de decir, ya es.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
是的，它发生在你身上。
Yes, it happens to you.
Sí, te pasa.
显然不是在无意识中。
Obviously not in the unconscious.
Obviamente en el inconsciente no.
生活中不能不考虑世界杯。
not to live without thinking about the World Cup.
no vivir sin pensar en la Copa del Mundo.
最接近的那些想法是......
that the closest those thoughts are...
que la vez más cerca esos pensamientos son...
它会多次浮现在你的脑海中，并且你会接受它。
It comes to mind many more times and you live with it.
Se te viene a la cabeza muchas más veces y se convive con eso.
带着恐惧，带着不确定性，带着喜悦，带着很多能让你进入世界杯的东西。
with fears, with uncertainty, with joy, with a lot of things that lead you to a World Cup.
con los miedos, con la incertidumbre, con la alegría, con un montón de cosas que te llevan a una Copa del Mundo.
你必须进入名单。
You have to get on the list.
Hay que salir a la lista.
但就我而言，是的，显然非常有动力并且充满热情。
But for my part, yes, obviously very driven and with a lot of enthusiasm.
Pero yo de mi parte sí, obviamente muy manija y con mucha ilusión.
国家队又将成为主角。
that the national team is going to be the protagonist again.
que la selección va a ser protagonista otra vez.
但有多难，对吧？
But how difficult, right?
Pero qué difícil, ¿no?
是的，非常困难。
Yes, very difficult.
Sí, muy difícil.
因为我在想，明白吗？
Because I think about it, see?
Porque yo la pienso, ¿viste?
嘿，停下来，你已经赢得了一切。
Hey, stop, you've already won everything.
Che, para, ya se ganó todo.
这非常困难，但是嘿，让我们看看......
It's very difficult, but hey, let's see...
Es muy difícil, pero bueno, a ver...
我在同事们身上看到了信念。
I see conviction in my colleagues.
Veo en mis compañeros un convencimiento.
以及对继续发生的渴望。
and a hunger to keep happening.
y un hambre de seguir sucediendo.
我们赢得了美洲杯冠军，并且力争第二次。
We have won a Copa América and we went for the second.
Hemos ganado una Copa América y fuimos por la segunda.
我们赢得了决赛，我们想再次与西班牙比赛，当这似乎没有发生时，我们互相写信。
We won the final and we wanted to compete with Spain again and we wrote to each other when it seemed like it wasn't happening.
ganamos la finalísima y teníamos ganas de volver a competir con España y nos escribíamos cuando parecía que no se daba.
与本届世界杯一样，球队...
And the same with this World Cup, the team is...
Y lo mismo con esta Copa del Mundo, el equipo está...
他非常愿意放弃他所拥有的一切。
He is super willing to leave everything he has.
está súper predispuesto a dejar todo lo que tiene.
罗德里戈为什么去美国职业足球大联盟？
Why did Rodrigo go to the MLS?
¿Para qué fue Rodrigo la MLS?
因为竞争并不那么重要。
Because competition is not that important.
Porque la competencia no es tan importante.
你对此有何看法？
What do you think about that?
¿Qué opinas de eso?
因为还有一个人说，他毕竟是国家队球员。
Because there is also the other one who says, after all, he is a national team player.
Porque también está el otro que dice, depues es un jugador de selección.
如果你看到你的数字，在国家队你赢得了一切，在俱乐部你与国际马德里一起赢得了一切。
And if you see your number, in the national team you won everything and in clubs you won with Inter Madrid.
Y si ves tu número, en selección ganaste todo y en clubes ganaste con el Inter de Madrid.
国家队和俱乐部发生的事情令人难以置信。
It's incredible what happens with the national team and the clubs.
Es increíble lo que pasa con la selección y los clubes.
让我们看看，这些都是意见，而且非常值得尊敬。
Let's see, these are opinions and they are super respectable.
A ver, estas son opiniones y son súper respetables.
最重要的是因为他们谈论足球，这是一件好事。
more than all because they talk about football, which is the nice thing.
más que todo porque hablan de fútbol, que es lo lindo.
特别是我如何打球，如何滋养自己。
A lot particularly to how I play, how I nourish myself.
Mucho particularmente a cómo juego, cómo me nutro.
我知道今天我职业生涯中最重要的事情就是比赛。
I know that the most important thing in my career today is to play.
Yo sé que lo más importante hoy en mi carrera es jugar.
尝试尽可能多地玩游戏，这对我来说就是……
Try to play as many games as possible and that's what's going to do for me...
Intentar jugar la mayor cantidad de partidos posible y eso es lo que a mí me va a...
给予我所需要的，也就是身体上的
to give what I need, which is to be physically
a dar lo que necesito, que es estar físicamente
基本上，除了足球或其他事情之外，我还能得到国家队一直需要的东西。
to have what the national team always needed from me, basically, beyond football or other things.
para disponer de lo que siempre necesitó la selección de mí, básicamente, más allá del fútbol o de otras cosas.
所以我决定参加世界杯一年半。
So I decided to play in the World Cup for a year and a half.
Entonces yo me propuse un año y medio de la Copa del Mundo jugar.
比赛是发生在我身上的事情，我每三天就比赛一次，我没有受伤。
Playing is happening to me, I play every three days, I had no injuries.
Jugar se me está dando, juego cada tres días, no tuve lesiones.
我过得很开心，有时我什至会告诉你
I'm having a great time, I would even tell you that sometimes
Llevo en un gran momento, hasta te diría que a veces
甚至比其他比赛还要好。
even better than in other competitions.
hasta mejor que en otras competiciones.
这很好，因为它取消了不参加冠军联赛的条件。
That's good, because it deactivates the che to not play in the Champions League.
Eso es bueno, porque desactiva el che para no jugar a la Champions.
让我们看看，不踢欧冠，你连欧冠都不踢。
Let's see, don't play the Champions League, you don't even play the Champions League.
A ver, no jugar la Champions, ni la Champions juegas.
一年六七场比赛。
Six or seven games in a year.
Seis o siete partidos en un año.
这并不是那么超然。
It's not that transcendental.
No es tan trascendental.
我知道这是一场令人难以置信的竞争，充满活力......
I understand that it is an incredible competition and the dynamics...
Entiendo que es una competencia increíble y la dinámica...
欧洲有很多积极的东西。
What Europe has, it has a lot of positive things.
que tiene Europa, tiene un montón de cosas positivas.
在我看来，我认为我需要这样，在我的腿上几分钟。
The way I see it, I think I need that, minutes in my legs.
A mi manera de verlo yo creo que necesito eso, minutos en las piernas.
前一段时间我们和他讨论过，看看他是如何抵达阿根廷的。
We talked about it a while ago with him, to see how he arrives in Argentina.
Lo hablamos hace un rato con él, para ver cómo llega a Argentina.
你和Leo谈论世界杯吗？
Do you talk to Leo about the World Cup?
¿Vos hablás con Leo del Mundial?
许多可能发生的事情和不可能发生的事情，因为
much of what can happen and what cannot happen because
mucho de lo que puede pasar y lo que no puede pasar porque
我想必须有人推动他，你必须给他施加压力。
I imagine that someone has to push him, you have to pressure him.
Imagino que alguien lo tiene que puxar, vos lo tienes que presionar a él.
与其说是这样，不如说是我们希望如此。
Not so much in that, but in the hope we have.
No tanto en eso, si en la ilusión que tenemos.
我们也有准备，我不知道他能不能应付，但是两三个月前……
We also prepared for that, I don't know if he can handle it, but two or three months ago...
También nos preparamos para eso, no sé si capaz se motonea, pero hace dos o tres meses...
每天我们都有一个超出我们在俱乐部所做的训练计划，我们都自杀了。
that every day we have a training plan beyond what we do at the club and we both kill ourselves.
que todos los días tenemos un plan de entrenamiento más allá de lo que hacemos en el club y los dos nos matamos.
以身体达到最佳方式。
to physically reach the best way.
para físicamente llegar a la mejor manera.
我们有双班制，...
We have a double shift that...
Tenemos un doble turno que...
我们开始这样做，我们有我们的老师，我们在那里给予它，我们做得很好。
We set out to do it and we have our teacher and we give it there and we do well.
que nos lo propusimos y tenemos nuestro profe y ahí le damos y venimos bien.
这是一份脱离俱乐部的工作。
It is a job apart from the club.
Es un trabajo aparte del club.
这是一份思考世界杯的工作。
-  -
那挺好的。
It is a job thinking about the World Cup.
Es un trabajo pensando en el Mundial.
我在里面放了一个小电影，看到了吗？
That's good.
Eso está bueno.
我把一切都拍下来。
I put a little movie in it, see?
Yo metiéndole un poco de peli, ¿viste?
怎么是电影呢？
I film everything.
Lo filmo todo.
我拍摄了一切，我说，我不知道。
How is it a movie?
¿Cómo es peli?
不，让你拍我吧。
And I film everything, I say, I don't know.
Y filmo todo, digo, yo no sé.
他们已经或者能够这样做。
-  -
那！
No, let you film me.
No, deja que me filmás.
一件事。
They have or are able to do so.
Tienen o capaz que si se da.
我和你的一个有过接触，我认为是宫内节育器，它激励你，我认为它是在卡塔尔，它激励你并告诉你，你以前在哪里训练过？
That!
¡Eso!
嗯，是的，萨兰迪。
One thing.
Una cosa.
一半是史诗，一半是我以为是你。
I crossed paths with one of yours, which I think is the IUD, which motivates you, I think it's in Qatar, it motivates you and tells you, where did you train before?
crucé con uno tuyo, que creo que es el DIU, que te motiva, creo que es en Qatar, te motiva y te dice, ¿dónde entrenabas antes?
我已经知道是哪一个了，是的，那是在选举日。
And well, yes, Sarandí.
Y bueno, sí, Sarandí.
你必须激励他。
and half epic, half that I thought it was you.
y medio épico, medio que yo me creía que era vos.
是的。
Yes.
Sí.
无论如何你都应该这样做，对吧？
You should do it anyway, right?
Igual lo debes hacer, ¿no?
是的，我在里面装了一个充气机就死了。
Yes, I put an inflator in it to die.
Sí, yo le meto inflador a morir.
也许他也是，因为他比我线性得多，我的情绪起伏很大，所以我有很多低落的时刻，而他……
Maybe he too, because he is much more linear than me, I am a lot of up and down so I have a lot of low moment and he...
igual él también, porque él es mucho más lineal que yo, yo soy mucho de arriba y de abajo entonces tengo mucho momento bajo y él me...
啊，我认为你总是在最上面。
Ah, I think you are always on top.
Ah, yo creo que vos siempre estás arriba.
当你倒下时，有人告诉你...
When you go down, someone tells you...
Cuando vas a la baja, alguien te dice…
当我倒下时，我就倒下。
When I go down, I go down.
Cuando voy a la baja, voy a la baja.
啊，低就是低。
-  -
是的。
Ah, low is low.
Ah, la baja es baja.
他是线性的，明白吗？
Yes.
Sí.
他或多或少总是保持一条线。
He is linear, see?
Él es lineal, ¿viste?
那么，好吧。
He more or less always maintains a line.
Él más o menos siempre mantiene una línea.
我们互补性很好。
So, well.
Entonces, bueno.
我喜欢它。
We complement each other well.
Nos complementamos bien.
我知道你永远不想说出确切的日期，因为你不知道，但你想说的是不会发生的事情。
I like it.
Me gusta.
但你正在考虑在某个时候重返赛车队，因为劳塔罗前几天告诉我......
I know you never want to say an exact date because you don't know, but you want to say things that are not going to happen.
Sé que nunca querés decir una fecha exacta porque no lo sabés, sino querés decir cosas que no van a suceder.
米利托烧了头，科斯塔斯烧了头，科斯塔斯还说他经常给你打电话。
But you are thinking about returning to Racing at some point, because Lautaro told me the other day that...
Pero tenés pensado en la vuelta a Racing en algún momento, porque Lautaro el otro día me contó que...
是的，好吧，现实是这是我喜欢的东西
Milito burns his head, Costas burns his head and Costas also said that he calls you often.
Milito le quema la cabeza, que Costas le quema la cabeza y Costas también dijo que a vos te llama seguido.
但我想说，我不是一个灰色或冷漠的人。
Yes, well, the reality is that it is something that I would love
Sí, bueno, la realidad es que a mí es algo que me encantaría
但我也必须从我的位置上理解我正在玩的冗余游戏。
But I'm not a gray or lukewarm guy, I'd love to say.
Pero no soy un tipo ni gris ni tibio, me encantaría decirlo.
多一个或少一个字，人们就很难理解。
that one more or less word is difficult for people to understand.
que una palabra de más o de menos a la gente le cuesta entender.
我们正在改变我们的观点或生活动态。
that we are changing our opinions or dynamics of life.
que vamos cambiando de opiniones o dinámicas de la vida.
当你曾经说过的事情发生在你身上并且人们成长时，他们就会进化。
When something that you once said happens to you and people grow, they evolve.
Cuando te pasa algo que dijiste alguna vez y la gente crece, evoluciona.
改变你的想法。
changes your mind.
cambia de parecer.
所以我不想成为我言语的囚徒。
So I don't want to be a prisoner of my words.
Entonces no quiero ser preso de mis palabras.
我觉得他们支持我...
I think they support me...
creo que me avalan...
我的职业生涯，因为我总是把比赛放在第一位，有一天我想再次参加南美解放者杯比赛。
my career, as I always put Racing before everything, the day I wanted to play in the Copa Libertadores again.
mi trayectoria, como siempre puse a Racing delante de todo, el día que quise volver a jugar una Copa Libertadores.
当我 20 岁时在巴伦西亚我做到了。
When I was 20 years old in Valencia I did it.
Con 20 años estando en Valencia lo hice.
现在我决定离开欧洲来到国际米兰。
Now I made the decision to leave Europe to come to Inter.
Ahora tomé la decisión de salir de Europa para venir al Inter.
我立即做出决定，并对后果负责。
I make decisions in the moment and I take responsibility for the consequences.
Las decisiones las tomo en el momento y me hago cargo de las consecuencias.
如果我喜欢它，是的，我会喜欢它。
If I would love it, yes, I would love it.
Si me encantaría, sí, me encantaría.
日期或者是否会发生......
Date or if it will happen...
Fecha o si va a suceder...
我不知道。
I don't know.
No lo sé.
我不会创造合乎逻辑的未来。
I don't make logical future.
No hago futuro lógico.
他们打电话给你，他们打电话给你。
They call you, they call you.
Que te llaman, te llaman.
他打电话给我，他打电话给我。
He calls me, he calls me.
Me llama, me llama.
我和迭戈交谈，我和奇诺交谈。
I talk to Diego, I talk to Chino.
Hablo con Diego, hablo con el Chino.
和古斯塔沃一起，当我去找蒂塔时，他也挤了我一下。
With Gustavo, when I went to Tita, he also squeezed me a little.
Con Gustavo, cuando fui al Tita, también me apretó un poquito.
我看着这里的人。
I'm looking at the guys who are here.
Estoy viendo a los chicos que están acá.
如果明天……上帝保佑，他们还很年轻。
If tomorrow one... God forbid, they are very young.
Si el día de mañana uno... Dios no quiera, son muy jóvenes.
四和七。
Four and seven.
Cuatro y siete.
Yes, almost five and seven, yes.
Sí, casi cinco y siete, sí.
Five and eight, I'll say.
Cinco y ocho, voy a decir.
如果明天是剃须刀的话...
If tomorrow is Shavel...
Si el día de mañana es Shavel...
She falls for you with a Rodrigo de Paul.
Ella te cae con un Rodrigo de Paul.
银行？
Banks?
¿Bancás?
I mean, she's 18, she says, Dad.
Es decir, ella tiene 18 años, dice, papá.
我男朋友来了，你看到他进来，你就会说，哇，这就是小时候的我。
My boyfriend comes and you see him enter and you say, wow, that's me as a kid.
Viene mi novio y vos lo ves entrar y decís, uy boludo, soy yo de chico.
你在吗？
Are you in?
¿Estás adentro?
是的，如果她爱他……不，但你明白这个问题。
Yes, if she loves him... No, but you understand the question.
Sí, si ella lo ama… No, pero vos entendés la pregunta.
今天我会说100%。
Today I would say 100%.
En el hoy te diría que 100%.
尤其是因为...
Especially because...
Sobre todo por...
年轻人对坏事的亲近感。
The closeness that young people have with bad things.
La cercanía que tienen los jóvenes con cosas malas.
that there are more and more.
que cada vez hay más.
在那里他生活得非常健康，因为我一直是一名运动员。
In that place he lives super healthy because I have always been an athlete.
En ese lugar vive súper sano porque siempre fui deportista.
嗯，是的，但你不会成为一个嫉妒的爸爸。
Well, yes, but you're not going to be a jealous dad.
Bien, sí, pero no vas a ser un papá celoso.
就像你看到了发生的事情并触摸了它一样。
Like you saw what happened and you put a touch on it.
Como que viste que pasa y le metés un toco.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
他是一个嫉妒的父亲。
He is a jealous dad.
Es un papá celoso.
但现在怎么知道这样有点恶心呢？
But how can it be now that I know that that's a bit disgusting?
Pero ¿cómo puede ser ya ahora que sepa que eso es un poco asinoso?
It's very strange, but...
Es rarísimo, pero…
只要说我是否愿意做他们做过的一件事。
Just say if I'm going to have one thing they've done.
Sólo diga que si voy a tener una cosa que hayan hecho.
啊，我要告诉你，以防你听不到。
Ah, I'm going to tell it, in case you don't hear it.
Ah, lo voy a contar yo, por si no se escucha.
Of course, I just asked De Paul...
Claro, yo le acabo de preguntar a De Paul...
如果他是熊，他告诉我，不，chiquen，他不会走，弗兰在这里，他说……
If he is the bear and he tells me, no, chiquen, he's not going, Fran is here and he says...
si él es el oso y él me dice, no, chiquen, no va, que está Fran acá y dice...
这正是你女儿说的，不是我说的。
This is exactly what your daughter said, I didn't say it.
Esto tal cual lo dijo tu hija, no lo dije yo.
我问他我是否可以找男朋友，他告诉我不行，只有当我40岁的时候。
I asked him if I could have a boyfriend and he told me no, only when I'm 40.
Yo le pregunté si podía tener novio y él me dijo que no, recién cuando tenga 40.
No, what you did is very wrong.
No, está muy mal eso que hiciste.
40！
40!
¡40!
I think he made a reasonable one.
Yo creo que hizo una razonable.
Did he tell you that?
-  -
是的。
Did he tell you that?
¿Te dijo eso?
It's a lot of 40, Rodri, you have to...
Yes.
Sí.
Yes we talked about it yesterday.
It's a lot of 40, Rodri, you have to...
Es mucho 40, Rodri, tenés que...
It's burning you, okay.
Yes we talked about it yesterday.
Si lo hablamos ayer.
Yesterday or last night?
-  -
是的。
It's burning you, okay.
Te está quemando, va.
But then we reached another agreement.
Yesterday or last night?
¿Ayer o anoche?
He is not telling that part.
Yes.
Sí.
At 20 we met.
But then we reached another agreement.
Pero después llegamos a otro acuerdo.
No, it's wrong of you.
No, está mal de tu parte.
也许我不会介入你的……你介入了吗？
Maybe I'm not going to get involved in your... Are you getting involved?
Igual yo no me voy a meter en tu... ¿Te estás metiendo?
是的，但是……
Yes, but...
Sí, pero...
At the end of the day I'm not getting in, I'm combing from the outside.
Al fin y al cabo no me estoy metiendo, estoy peinando de afuera.
从外面看，那是什么，白痴？
And what is that, combing from the outside, idiot?
¿Y qué es eso, peinar de afuera, boludo?
进来吧，我们去看比赛吧，完成它
Get in Exactly, let's go to the games and finish it
Meterte Exactamente, vamos a los juegos y lo terminamos
Because the note we made about the Lukes was so popular, we won a prize.
Porque como garpó mucho la nota que hicimos de los Luke, ganamos un premio.
我不知道，你没有感谢我。
I don't know, you didn't thank me.
No sé, que no me agradeciste.
我确实感谢过的一个偶像。
An idol I did thank you for.
Un ídolo sí que te agradecí.
When did you go up?
¿Cuándo subiste?
Yes, an apple.
Sí, una manzana.
为什么要说一些你没看到的事情呢？
Why do you say something you didn't see?
¿Por qué decís algo que no viste?
我不喜欢这样...我赌博了，对不起，对不起。
I don't like that... I gambled, sorry, sorry.
No me gusta que... Me la jugué, perdón, perdón.
我谢谢你，我也爱你。
I thanked you, I loved you too.
Te lo agradecí, te arrobé también.
But I had told you, I told you, you will see that with this note... Do you remember?
Pero yo te lo había dicho, te dije, vas a ver que con esta nota... ¿Te acordás?
那张纸条进展顺利。
That note went very well.
Esa nota le fue muy bien.
你告诉我，不，因为看，这个有八百万，四百万，我告诉你，女孩，别动。
And you told me, no, because look, this one has eight million, four million, and I told you, girl, stay still.
Y me dijiste, no, porque mirá, este tiene ocho millones, cuatro millones, y yo te dije, chica, quédate quieto.
我要告诉你一件事，直到这里，直到这里，因为我的生活是潘多拉的盒子。
I'm going to tell you one thing, up to here, up to here, because my life is Pandora's box.
Te voy a decir una cosa, hasta acá, hasta acá, porque mi vida es la caja de Pandora.
这是我最喜欢做的笔记。
It is the note that I liked doing the most.
es la nota que más me gustó hacer.
And if.
Y sí.
不是，怎么会是呢？
No, how is it yes?
No, ¿cómo es sí?
我在家里把你照顾得很好。
I took good care of you at home.
Te atendí bien en casa.
你把我照顾得很好。
You took good care of me.
Me atendiste bien.
不，你一直都很照顾我。
No, you always take good care of me.
No, siempre me atendés bien.
嗯，我们发布了非常相似的照片。
Well, we posted very similar photos.
Bueno, pusimos fotos muy parecidas.
罗德里戈·德·保罗和贝克汉姆的作品，因为有空气，就有东西。
of Rodrigo de Paul and Beckham, because there is an air, there is something.
de Rodrigo de Paul y Beckham, porque hay un aire, hay un algo.
你必须告诉我谁赢了。
You have to tell me who wins.
Vos me tenés que decir quién gana.
两种造型，准备好了吗？
of the two looks, ready?
de los dos looks, ¿listo?
给吧。
Give it.
Dale.
你能做到吗？
-  -
是的。
Are you up to it?
¿Estás para hacerlo?
小心点，别说谎。
-  -
一点也不。
Yes.
Sí.
谁赢了？
Be careful, don't lie.
Ojo, no mientas.
罗德里戈·德·保罗还是大卫？
Not at all.
Para nada.
大卫.
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
大卫.
Rodrigo de Paul or David?
¿Rodrigo de Paul o David?
那里非常好。
David.
无论如何，在我看来，我的肩膀上武装得更多一些。
谁赢了？
It's very good there.
Está muy bien ahí.
大卫赢了吗？
Does David win?
¿David gana?
第一个是芹菜画家大卫？
The first is the celerist David?
¿La primera la celerista David?
匹配或输掉。
Match or lost.
Partido o perdido.
我会把它交给大卫。
I'll give it to David.
Se la voy a David.
是的，我要去大卫那里。
Yes, I'm going to David.
Sí, se la voy a David.
现在看，她没有，不，不，你女儿没有给你监护人。
Look now, she doesn't, no, no, your daughter doesn't give you guardians.
Mira ahora, ella no, no, no, tu hija no te da guardas.
谁赢了？
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
这就是您参加迈阿密国际发布会的方式。
This is how you went to the presentation of Inter Miami.
Así fuiste a la presentación del Inter de Miami.
我重新创建了它。
I recreated it.
Lo recreé.
是的，我意识到了。
Yes, I realized it.
Sí, me dí cuenta.
很好。
It's nice.
Es lindo.
我尝试一下。
I try.
Lo intento.
你疯了吗？
You're crazy?
¿Estás loco?
还有……还有……还有……
and... and... and...
y... y... y...
让我们看看。
-  -
非常好。
Let's see.
A ver.
我感觉
Very good.
Muy bien.
它会欺骗人！
I feel
Siento yo.
酷炫表演！
And it deceives!
¡Y engana!
一件一件的，很简单。
Cool Show!
¡Chulio Show!
看看他和那个混蛋是什么关系，孩子！
-  -
不？
再见。
Look what he is, kid, with that asshole!
¡Mira lo que es él, chabón, con ese asbo!
你去了。
No?
吉尔.
Bye.
Chau.
不，看看这个。
You went.
Fuiste.
非常九十年代，非常后街男孩。
-  -
让我们来看看。
Gil.
谁偷窃？
No, look at this one.
No, mira esta.
大卫或罗德里戈。
Very nineties, very Backstreet Boys.
Muy noventosa, muy Backstreet Boys.
没有人偷窃。
Let's see.
A ver.
这就是谁赢了。
-  -
清除。
Who steals?
¿Quién roba?
好了好了，停下来吧。
David or Rodrigo.
David o Rodrigo.
不，大卫。
There is no one who steals.
No hay quién roba.
谁赢了？
It's who wins.
Es quien gana.
大卫.
Clear.
Claro.
大卫，你的孩子们不同意。
Well, well, stop.
Bueno, bueno, pará.
你会输的。
No, David.
戴维，在这个戴维。
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
在这个戴维?
In this Davy?
¿En esta Davy?
你不好吗？
Are you bad?
¿Vos malo?
不，但在 Lope 中，我正处于过渡期，希望能拥有更长的时间。
No, but in the Lope I was in the transition to have it long.
No, pero en el Lope yo estaba en la transición para tenerlo largo.
你看到中间是最糟糕的时候。
And you saw that in the middle was the worst time.
Y viste que en el medio la peor época.
所以我不喜欢中间人对我的看法。
So I didn't like how the middle looked on me.
Entonces no me gustaba cómo me quedaba la mitad.
这就是为什么你把它放进去……你尝试了凝胶……大卫赢了。
That's why you put it in... you tried gel... David wins.
Por eso le metías… probás con gomina… Gana David.
2比1。
2 to 1.
2 a 1.
大卫和罗德里谁赢了？
Who wins, David or Rodri?
¿Quién gana, David o Rodri?
我。
I.
Yo.
不，来吧。
No, come on.
No, dale.
但看看他是什么人，白痴。
But look what he is, idiot.
Pero mira lo que es él, boludo.
鸡，别这么卑鄙，白痴。
Chicken, don't be mean, idiot.
Pollo, no seas malo, boludo.
看看我怎么样。
Look how I am.
Mira cómo estoy.
像90年代的类型，颜色。
type like the 90s, the color.
tipo como los 90, el color.
我们现在是 2026 年。
We are in 2026.
Estamos en el 2026.
我知道，但一切都会回来。
I know, but all that is coming back.
Ya sé, pero está volviendo todo eso.
你也醒醒吧。
You wake up too.
Vos despertate también.
别跟我争论时尚。
Don't argue with me about fashion.
No me discutás de moda.
我火花四射，我学习。
I spark, I study.
Yo chispeo, estudio.
但这是一场斗争。
But this is a struggle.
Pero esto es un afano.
他半倒在这儿，烦人。
He was half fallen here, annoying.
Él estaba medio caído acá fastidioso.
他让我生气。
He makes me angry.
Me da la cara enojado.
两两发生了。
Two by two it happens.
Dos a dos pasa.
两对二？
Two to two?
¿Dos a dos?
还剩多少？
How many are left?
¿Cuántas quedan?
我们还剩两个。
We have two left.
Nos quedan dos.
不，你在烤箱里。
No, here you are in the oven.
No, es que acá estás al horno.
你在烤箱里。
Here you are in the oven.
Acá estás al horno.
我很庆幸我没有提出下面所说的评论。
And I was grateful that I didn't bring the comment I said below.
Y agradecé que no traje el comentario que decía acá abajo.
这是来自你的 Instagram，演员。
It's from your Instagram, actor.
Es de tu Instagram, actor.
你看到了，你就死了。
You see that, you die.
Ves eso, te morís.
标签...我不会告诉你。
Hashtag... I'm not going to tell you.
Hashtag... No te lo voy a decir.
啊，你在这里。
Ah, here you are.
Ah, acá estás.
在国家B.
In the national B.
En la B nacional.
下面。
-  -
再见。
Below.
Abajo.
谁赢了？
Bye.
Chao.
罗德里戈还是大卫？
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
这不是为了乱搞。
Rodrigo or David?
¿Rodrigo o David?
这是另一个时间了。
It's not to mess around.
No es para joder.
这是你的 Instagram。
It's your Instagram.
Es tu Instagram.
我告诉你他赢了。
I tell you he wins.
Te digo que gana él.
谁赢了？
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
你的表情很奇怪，孩子。
Your look is strange, kid.
Es raro tu look, chabón.
你知道凯特做了什么吗？
Do you know what Kat did?
¿Sabes qué hacía Kat?
那个还是用的。
That was still used.
Igual se usaba eso.
将使用什么？
What is going to be used?
¿Qué se va a usar?
那是15年前的事了！
That was 15 years ago!
¡Ello fue hace 15 años!
但用的时候……看，看，看。
But when it was used... Look, look, look.
Pero cuando se usó… Mirá, mirá, mirá.
另外，我刚到欧洲，所有品牌都买了。
Besides, I just arrived in Europe, I bought all the brands.
Aparte, recién llegué a Europa, me compré todas las marcas.
你的胡子更适合你。
Your beard looks better on you.
Te queda mejor la barba.
没有胡子，皮肤白。
No beard, white.
Sin barba, blanco.
来吧，疯了。
Come on, crazy.
Pasala, loco.
来吧，来吧，传递下去。
Come on, come on, pass it on.
Dale, dale, pasala.
我对那件事并不疯狂。
I wasn't crazy about that one.
No me encané con esa.
我有一百张照片，他想把那一张留一个小时……最后一张！
There are a hundred photos of me and he wants to leave that one for an hour... The last one!
Hay cien fotos mías bien y quiere dejar esa una hora en la... ¡La última!
谁赢了？
Who wins?
¿Quién gana?
罗德里戈或大卫。
Rodrigo or David.
Rodrigo o David.
法老？
Pharaoh?
¿Faraó?
不，越位。
No, offside.
No, fuera de juego.
严重地。
-  -
Seriously.
Hala en serio.
我真的很告诉你。
Seriously.
Hala en serio.
视频请严肃点。
I'm really telling you.
De verdad te lo digo.
我杀了他，我杀了他。
The video please be serious.
El video por favor que sea serio.
但是看看，看看这家伙的优雅。
I killed him, I killed him.
Lo maté, lo maté.
给吧。
But look, look at the elegance of the guy.
Pero mira, mira la elegancia del chabón.
是这样的。
Give it.
Dale.
我们有三首蒂尼歌曲。
This is so.
Esto es así.
她是你的女朋友，你还没有结婚，但你要结婚了。
We have three Tini songs.
Tenemos tres temas de Tini.
我要告诉你这首歌是怎么说的，我想知道你是否知道它的结尾。
that she is your girlfriend, that you didn't get married, but that you are going to get married.
que es tu novia, que no te casaste, pero que te vas a casar.
给吧。
I'm going to tell you how the song says and I want to know if you know how it ends.
Yo te voy a decir cómo dice la canción y quiero saber si vos la sabés cómo termina.
但我不会告诉你它是唱的，这更容易。
-  -
好的。
Give it.
Dale.
因为我也知道Tini的歌。
-  -
好的。
But I'm not going to tell you it sung, it's easier.
Pero no te la voy a decir con la cantada, que es más fácil.
你能做到吗？
-  -
是的。
Okay.
Ok.
开始了。
Because I also know Tini's songs.
Porque yo también sé temas de Tini.
我们怎么了？
Okay.
Ok.
当我们身体好的时候，事情就变得复杂了。
that when we were well it became complicated.
que cuando estábamos bien se complicó.
如下？
As follows?
¿Cómo sigue?
当我们健康的时候，事情就会变得复杂
when we are well it gets complicated
cuando estamos bien se complico
停下来，停下来。
Stop, stop.
Para, para.
不，我们如何开始？
-  -
为了。
No, how do we start?
No, cómo arrancamos.
不，不，不，不
For.
Para.
我们非常相爱，现在丘比特射出了一支箭......
No, no, no, no
是的，完美！
We loved each other so much and now Cupid shot an arrow and...
Que nos queríamos tanto y ahora no Cupido tiró una flecha y la...
主题的名称是什么？
Yes, perfect!
¡Sí, perfecto!
丘比特。
-  -
出色的。
What is the name of the theme?
¿Cómo se llama el tema?
嗯，但这非常...
Cupid.
Cupido.
好吧，罗德里戈·德·波尔特（Rodrigo de Polte）。
Excellent.
Excelente.
来吧，对我撒谎。
Well, but that's very...
Bueno, pero eso es muy...
和我一起做你想做的事吧。
Well, point for Rodrigo de Polte.
Bien, punto para Rodrigo de Polte.
不值得唱。
-  -
为了。
Come on, lie to me.
Dale, miénteme.
告诉我是否有损坏，已经有两个了。
Do what you want with me.
Haz lo que tú quieras conmigo.
这个更嗡嗡响。
It's not worth singing it.
No vale que la cante.
这是我不知道的一点……不不，不是那样的。
It's a point I don't know... No, no, it's not like that.
Es un punto que no sé... No, no, no es así.
不，你哼了一声。
No, you hummed it.
No, vos la tarareaste.
告诉我今晚我是你的宝贝。
Tell me that tonight I am your baby.
Dime que esta noche yo soy tu bebé.
那又怎样呢？
And what about?
¿Y qué tal?
我就是你。
I am you.
Yo soy tú.
稍后你...明天我们就是朋友了。
And you later... And tomorrow we are friends.
Y vos después... Y mañana somos amigos.
虽然明天我们...
Although tomorrow we are...
Aunque mañana somos...
朋友，朋友！
Friend, friend!
¡Amigo, amigo!
嗯，我想...
Well, I guess...
Bueno, supongo que…
嗯，我不知道。
Well, I don't know.
Bueno, no sé.
再来一张。
One more.
Una más.
昨天下雨了。
Yesterday it rained.
Ayer llovió.
在布宜诺斯艾利斯。
in Buenos Aires.
en Buenos Aires.
如下？
As follows?
¿Cómo sigue?
现在...太棒了！
And now... Excellent!
Y ahora... ¡Excelente!
这就是生活的意义。
That's what life is about.
De eso se trata la vida.
最后，请给我喝一杯，妈妈。
And lastly, serve me a drink, ma.
Y la última, sírveme un traguito, ma.
一份给我，一份给我。
One for me and one for me.
Uno pa' mí y otro pa'.
我认为你读起来好像...
I think you're reading as if...
Creo que estás leyendo como si...
我正想搞死你，白痴。
I'm trying to screw you, idiot.
Estoy tratando de cagarte, boludo.
给我倒一杯饮料。
Pour me a drink.
Sírveme un traguito.
怎么样？
-  -
再次。
How is?
¿Cómo es?
再给我倒一杯酒。
Again.
Otra vez.
一份给我，一份给我。
Pour me one more drink.
Sírveme un traguito más.
这是一个很棒的话题，除此之外。
-  -
是的。
One for me and one for me.
Uno pa' mí y otro pa'.
三重。
It's a great topic, apart.
Es un temazo, aparte.
这是三重，就像……是的，你说的是。
-  -
为了。
Yes.
Sí.
告诉我最后两部分的最后一部分。
The triple.
La triple.
妈妈，给我倒杯饮料。
It's the triple, like... Yes, you say it.
Es la triple, como… Sí, lo decís.
一份给我，一份给我。
For.
Para.
还有一个。
Tell me the last part of the last two.
Decíreme la última parte de la última dos.
你出去了吗？
Pour me a drink, ma.
Sírveme un traguito, ma.
有时忘记生命只有一次的人说道。
One for me and one for me.
Uno pa' mí y otro pa'.
这将是一种生活。
And another pa'.
Y otro pa'.
是的，是的。
-  -
好的。
完美的。
Are you out?
¿Estás fuera?
嘿嘿，有一个就很好了。
Hey, one is very good.
Che, uno es muy bien.
三对一。
-  -
作为？
Three to one.
Tres a uno.
三对一。
As?
¿Cómo?
不，批准了。
Three to one.
Tres a uno.
很好，罗德里。
-  -
出色的。
No, approved.
No, aprobado.
就这样吧，已经痛了。
Very good, Rodri.
Muy bien, Rodri.
你是一个很棒的人，我想在便条中告诉你。
Excellent.
Excelente.
我希望你能出来，你是一个很棒的人。
-  -
谢谢。
That's it, it already hurt.
Ya está, ya dolió.
你们都是好人，大家都爱你们。
You are a great guy, I want to tell you in the note.
Sos un gran tipo, te lo quiero decir en la nota.
你们有着非常牢固的联系，这很重要，特别是对我来说，你一直是一个很棒的人，所以我现在想在这里感谢你。
-  -
谢谢。
I want you to come out, you're a great guy.
Quiero que salgas, sos un gran tipo.
我也爱你。
Thank you.
Gracias.
谢谢，罗德里。
You are good people, everyone loves you.
Sos buena gente, todo el mundo te quiere.
谢谢，爸爸。
You have very strong ties, which is important, and particularly with me you were always a great guy, so I want to thank you here now.
tenés vínculos muy fuertes, que eso es importante, y particularmente conmigo siempre fuiste un tipazo, así que te lo quiero agradecer ahora acá.
掌声也热烈。
-  -
谢谢你！
Thank you.
Gracias.